[
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [87, 89, 84, 82, 86, 85, 88, 83, 83, 81, 83]?",
      "correctAnswer": "83",
      "options": [
        "82",
        "83",
        "84",
        "85"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [90, 82, 85, 83, 83, 87, 89, 83, 84, 88, 83, 86]?",
      "correctAnswer": "83",
      "options": [
        "82",
        "83",
        "84",
        "85"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [87, 88, 89, 84, 84, 91, 83, 90, 86, 84, 85, 84, 84]?",
      "correctAnswer": "84",
      "options": [
        "83",
        "84",
        "85",
        "86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [88, 90, 89, 86, 87, 86, 91, 92, 85, 84, 86]?",
      "correctAnswer": "86",
      "options": [
        "85",
        "86",
        "87",
        "88"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [87, 89, 92, 89, 88, 89, 93, 86, 89, 85, 90, 91]?",
      "correctAnswer": "89",
      "options": [
        "88",
        "89",
        "90",
        "91"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [90, 94, 92, 89, 92, 93, 92, 86, 88, 91, 92, 92, 87]?",
      "correctAnswer": "92",
      "options": [
        "91",
        "92",
        "93",
        "94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [88, 91, 94, 90, 94, 94, 89, 87, 92, 95, 93]?",
      "correctAnswer": "94",
      "options": [
        "93",
        "94",
        "95",
        "96"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [88, 92, 92, 89, 92, 91, 94, 95, 90, 96, 92, 93]?",
      "correctAnswer": "92",
      "options": [
        "91",
        "92",
        "93",
        "94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [89, 97, 89, 89, 89, 91, 94, 90, 92, 96, 93, 95, 89]?",
      "correctAnswer": "89",
      "options": [
        "88",
        "89",
        "90",
        "91"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [94, 94, 94, 93, 92, 90, 95, 97, 91, 96, 98]?",
      "correctAnswer": "94",
      "options": [
        "93",
        "94",
        "95",
        "96"
      ]
    }
]